Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Visual Images, 1889-2019 UPG.RG.60
ULS Greensburg
- Prints (PR), 1969-2014; V.
  - Anniversary (UPG), 1988 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    25th, Dinner.
  - Smart Growth Partnership of Westmoreland County (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    Photos: Graziani, Alexander J.; Royse, Carolyn; Poole, Beverly
  - Art Exhibit, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    "African Spirit in the New World". Dr. Frank McGlynn.
  - Art Exhibit, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    "African Spirit in the New World". Music and Dance Program.
  - Art Exhibit, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    "Portraits of the Andes." Victor Beltran, artist. Reception.
  - Art Exhibit, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    Thaddeus Moseley Sculpture Exhibit.
  - Art Exhibit, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    Thaddeus Moseley Sculpture Exhibit. Reception.
  - Art Works (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    Fort Ligonier by Anthony Dimino.
  - Art Works, July 30 - August 1, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    "Upward to the Light", stained glass mural by Terry Bengel. Tower, Millstein Library. Installation.
  - Art Works, 2005, 2011 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    "Upward to the Light". Views. 2005, May 22; View Summer 2011
  - Art Works, May 14, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    "Upward to the Light". The Dr. Paul Albert Chew Memorial Window. Dedication.
  - Athletic Department, 2009/2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2)
    Staff 2009/2010. Berich, Anthony, Dir. of Athletics and Recreation; Gallick, Chasady, Hd. Cheer/Dance Coach; Gelet, Carol, Hd. Women's Basketball Coach; Geter, Andy, Asst. Women's Basketball Coach; Giran, Jason, Asst. Men's Basketball Coach; Munchinski, Dana, Hd. Softball Coach, Senior Woman's Administrator; Ross, Patrick, Sports Information Dir.; Simms, Leroy, Hd. Volleyball Coach; Washburn, David, Asst. Men's Basketball Coach; Wawrzyniak, Ted, Hd. Men's Soccer Coach; Yetter, Jeromy, Hd. Men's Basketball Coach. n.b.: For individual photo of David Washburn, See: Prints--Portraits--UPG Staff.
  - Baseball (Men's), 1996-2011 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 2, Shelf 11, Box 1)
    See also: Oversize Prints.
    1996/97 Team Photo.
    1997/98 Team Photo.
    1998/99
    1990/00
    2000/01
    2001/02
    2002/03
    2003/04 [Roster Spring 2004]
    2004/05 [Roster Spring 2005]
    2005/06 [Roster Spring 2006]
    2006/07 [Roster Spring 2007]
    2007/08 [Roster Spring 2008]
    2008/09 [No photos in the UPG Archives]
    2009/10
    2010/11
  - Basketball (Men's), 1969-1973 (Cabinet 1, Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 1)
    1969/1970, 1970/1971, 1972/73 Miscellaneous team and individual team member photos.
    See also: 1998/1999 Old Timers from the 1970's.
    See also UPG.RG.21 Ser.: Sports. Basketball (Men's). Scrapbook 1969/1970 and Scrapbook 1972/1973 [Both scrapbooks housed in Utility Cabinet].
  - Basketball (Men's), 1996-2011 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 1)
    1996/97 Group Photo; Individual Team Member Photos.
    1997/98 Group Photo; Individual Team Member Photos.
    1998/99 Group Photo; Individual Team Member Photos.
    1998/99 AMCC (Allegheny Mountain Collegiate Conference) Men's Basketball Championship Team. [includes Negatives].
    1998/99 Game shots.
    1998/99 Old Timers from the 1970's. 1/30/99.
    1999/00 Group Photo; Individual Team Member Photos.
    1999/00 Game Shots. 11/29/99.
    1999/00 AMCC Champions. 2000.
    2000/01 Team Photo; Individual Team Member Photos.
    2001/02 Team Photo; Individual Team Member Photos.
    2001/02 Tip-off; play. 12/1/01
    2002/03 Team Photo; Individual Team Member Photos.
    2002/03 Season tip-off. Dec., 2002.
    2003/04
    2004/05
    2005/06
    2006/07
    2007/08
    2008/2009 No photos for this academic year in UPG Archives [faz]
    2009/2010 [Includes team photo with inscription "Dr. Smith, Thanks for all your support"]
    2010/2011
  - Basketball (Women's), 1996-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 1, Box 4)
    1996/97
    1997/98
    1999/00 Team Photo; Individual Team Member Photos.
    1999/00 Game shots. 11/29/99.
    2002/03 Season tip-off. Dec. 2002.
    2002/03 AMCC Championship Tournament. Champions 2003.
    2011/12
  - Basketball--40th Anniversary Game, January 31, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 4)
    UPG Men, Women Vs. UPBradford Men, Women, Peterson Events Ctr., UPGH, Oakland Campus
  - Basketball--Exhibition Game, November 1, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 4)
    Swedish team vs. UPG Bobcats.
  - Basketball Court (Outdoor), 1988 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 4)
    Construction.
  - Bateson, Dr. Catherine, October 3, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 1)
    Behavioral Science Academic Village. Margaret Mead House.
  - Baton Twirler, January 29, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 1)
    Trish Springman
  - Big Band Picnic, August 29, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 1)
    UPG Pres., Dr. Frank A. Cassell with Joseph Greuber, CEO Valley Dairy and UPG Ad. Bd. member.
  - Black History Month, March 15, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 1)
    Morris Dees, speaker. Reception. [includes Negative]
  - Black History Month, February 29, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 1)
    Andrew Stockey.
  - Bobcat, 2004, 2009/2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 1)
    [UPG Mascot--Logo. Gymnasium Floor, Chambers Hall. Dec. 2004]
    2009/2010 Kyle V. Bloser
  - Bridge by Rossetti House, June 20, 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 1)
    Repairs.
  - Bridge to Lynch Hall (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 2)
  - Buenrostro Azua, Eric, October 5, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 1)
    Scholarship from the Rotary Club.
  - Buildings [Facilities], 1970-2012
    See also: Construction/Renovation Projects 2010-2012
    - Academic VIillages, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 2)
      Steps [Stairs] to Upper Parking Lot. Construction.
    - Academic VIillages (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 2)
      Classroom
    - Behavioral Science Academic Village (Student Residence Complex, Phase II), July 2000-May 30, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 3, Box 2)
      Groundbreaking. Group Photo: P. Richard Ridilla, developer; Dr. Frank A. Cassell UPG President; Will Hoffman, Pres. UPG Student Government Association; Charles Ingmire, Project Manager; Dr. Mark D. McColloch, UPG Acting Vice President for Admin. Affairs. Construction.
    - Biology Laboratory (Smith Hall), April-September, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 3)
    - Biology/Chemistry/Physics Laboratory, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 3)
      Baseline. Mar. 4, 2002. Construction. May-Aug., 2002.
    - Cassell Hall [Frank A. Cassell Hall] (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 3)
      n.b. For construction photos, See: UPG.RG.60 Prints. Construction Projects 2010-2012. Sustainable Office and Classroom Building (S.O.C. Building).
    - Chambers Hall, June 10, 1997 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 2, Box 3)
      Exterior
      Interior
      Interior: 1 print showing plaque "The University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Health Center Donated by Dr. and Mrs. Leslie S. Pierce."
      Interior: 1 print showing dedication of plaque "in memory of W.R. Wagner"
      Renaming of Common Facilities Building to Chambers Hall. Dedication. Reception.
      See also: UPG.RG.60 Video Cassettes VC II.2
      See also: Construction Projects 2010-2012
    - Chambers Hall Cafeteria, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 3)
    - Chambers Hall Dining Area Renovation, June-August 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 3)
      Baseline Renovation
    - Chambers Hall Expansion, 2004-2005 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 4)
      Baseline gymnasium floor. 3/24/04. New gymnasium floor. Dining Room.
    - Chambers Hall Student Lounge, July-November 1999 (Microfilm-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 4)
      Construction Renovation
    - Chauffeur's Cottage (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 4)
      Later called: Psychology Bldg.; Pareto Hall; Pohl Bldg.: Plant Maintenance Bldg.
      See: Lynch House. Chauffeur's Cottage
    - Chemistry Laboratory, March 4, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 4)
      Baseline
    - College Hall, 1996-1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 2, Box 4)
      Exterior/Interior. 1996, 1997, 1999.
      Open House. Aug. 1996.
      Univ. of Pgh. Greensburg Campus Dormitory #2 Schematic Design Concept #3 Study
      See also: UPG.RG.60 FD1 College Hall. Graduate Room. Interior.
    - Computing Center [now McKenna Hall], December 1996-January 1997 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 1, Shelf 11)
      Construction. Dec. 1996-Jan. 1997. Exterior.
      See also: Oversize Prints. Buildings – McKenna Hall.
    - Faculty Office Building (FOB), 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 3)
      Exterior. Construction. Architectural rendering, Print of.
    - Ferguson Theater, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 1)
      Construction. Dedication. Reception.
    - Health Center [University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg] (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 1)
      Dr. George Ferguson Chambers with Dr. and Mrs. Leslie S. Pierce who donated the Center to UPG. undtd.
      See Oversized Prints.
    - Humanities Academic Village, October 13, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 2, Box 1)
      For Construction photos, See: Student Residence Complex (Dorm #4).
    - Library Garden, The [A Memorial Garden and Meditation Area] (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 4)
      See: UPG.RG.52 Buildings [Facilities] Library Garden, The:
      See UPG.RG.60 Ser.: Flash Drive [FD3]
    - Lyceum (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 4)
      See: Natural Sciences and New Technologies Academic Village.
    - Lynch Hall [Starboard Light], 1970-1997 (Map-case 1, Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 2, Box 4, Shelf 11, Box 1)
      Exterior. fNegative. undtd. See: UPG.RG.60 Oversize. [Housed in Map Case].
      Exterior See also: Oversize prints. [Housed in Map Case]
      Interior. See also: Oversize prints. [Housed in Map Case]
      Interior.
      Interior. Showing Classroom. [1970's]
      Interior. Showing Entrance Hall. [Housed in Map Case]
      Interior. Showing Office. [1970's?]
      Interior. Showing Staircase. [1970's?]
      Interior. Showing UPG Logo.
      Interior. Showing President's Office.
      Guard's Post. Entrance to Lynch Hall. 1983
      Lounge. Basement of Lynch Hall. ca. early 1970's
      First Snack Bar. Shows Mrs. Kantorick, Dorothy Weir's mother.
      Renovation (Interior) 1997
      Renovation (Roof, Chimney) 1997
      Retaining Wall. Construction. May-Aug. 1997.
      The Anniversary Garden at Starboard Light [undtd] [UPG.qRG.60 Housed in Map Case]
      See also: UPG Archives UPG.qRG.60 Prints. Lynch Family Album]
      Post Card. Color photo by Bob Herd. undtd.
    - Lynch Pool & Bathouse (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 2, Box 4)
    - McKenna Hall (formerly Computing Center), 1997-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 2, Box 4)
      Dedication. Reception. Exterior.
    - Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center, 2006-2007 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Microfilm-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 2)
      Groundbreaking 12/6/06 Construction 12/13/06-10/29/07 Dedication and Ribbon Cutting. Reception. 11/13/07
    - Millstein Library, 1993-2001 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 3, Box 2)
      Groundbreaking, Oct. 15, 1993. John Robertshaw, Dr. George F. Chambers, Jack H. Millstein
      Interior 1996, 1997, 2001
      Dedication. Reception. 5 May 1995
      Move into Millstein Library
      See also: Construction Projects 2010-2012 Millstein Library [prints of patio construction]
    - Millstein Library ITV (Interactive Television Room). (ML250), 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 2)
    - Natural Sciences and New Technologies Academic Village, 2000-2005 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 3)
      Construction Site. July, Aug., 2000
      Village Hall (The Lyceum) Groundbreaking. 17 Jan. 2001.
      Village Hall (The Lyceum) Construction. Jan.-May, 2001
      Village Hall (The Lyceum) Dedication. 5 Sept. 2001
      Village Hall (The Lyceum) Exterior 30 May 2001
      Dormitory (Westmoreland Hall) [Student Residence Facility]--Construction 2004-2005
    - Powers Hall, 1997-1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 1)
      Exterior. Dedication. Entrance Way. Construction. Drainage Ditch. Construction.
    - Quinn House (now Rossetti House), 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 3)
      Interior Exterior
    - Quinn House Greenhouse, 1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 3)
    - Ramsay Building (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 3, Box 3)
    - Refrigeration Room, May-June 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 3)
    - Robertshaw Hall, October 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 3, Box 3)
      Exterior (Prints) Exterior (Negatives) Interior (Prints) Interior (Negatives) Reconstruction of outside concrete stairs.
    - Rossetti House, 1998-2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 4)
      Historical Note: also known as Rossetti International House, Rossetti House for International Studies. Part of Humanities Academic Village. Formerly known as Quinn House, Terra House. Exterior 1998, 2000 Dedication. Reception. 5 Nov. 1999
    - Security Information Center (SIC), 1998-1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 4)
      Construction Exterior
    - Smith Hall (Science Building), 1970-1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 3, Box 4, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 4)
      Exterior. After renovation.
      Classrooms
      Smith Hall ca. late 1970's prior to renovation in 1996-1997.
      Renovations to Smith Hall. Oct. 1996-Mar. 17, 1997
      Renovations to Smith Hall. Mar. 18, 1997-1998
      Lounge Aug. 1999
    - Student Activity Center (SAC) [later Computing Center and then McKenna Hall], 1974 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 1)
      ca. 1970's Pres. Smith and students on future site reviewing architectural plans. 1974?
    - Student Books Center (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 1)
      Otterman St., Greensburg
    - Sustainable Office and Classroom Building (S.O.C.), 2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 2)
      See: Construction Projects 2010-2012 [Note: In February 2012 named "Frank A. Cassell Hall". For post construction information, See UPG.RG.52 Ser. Buildings/Failities. Cassell Hall [Frank A. Cassell Hall]].
    - Terra House [now known as Rossetti House], 1998-1999 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 2)
      Renovation. Dec. 1998-Aug. 1999
      Renovation. Fire Extinguisher System. Mar. 1999
      Construction. Sewer Lines. Oct. 1998-Jan. 1999
    - University Court, 1982-2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 3)
      Exterior (Prints) Exterior (Negatives)
      Exterior 1982, 1984
      Interior 1982, 1984
      Exterior. Interior. 1999
      Renovation. May-Aug. 2000
      Winter 1995/96
    - Vogel Building (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 1)
      Greensburg Exterior
    - Wagner Dining Hall (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 3)
      Dining Room Fireside Lounge
  - Campus Development Fund [1965 Greensburg Campus Development Fund] (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
  - Campus Clock (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Programs; UPG.RG.60 Video Cassette VC II.2
  - Campus Entrance Way, 1999-2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    Construction. Base Line. June, 1999.
    Construction. Aug. 2-Nov. 10, 1999.
    Construction. Signage. Nov. 1999.
    Construction. Left wall exiting campus. Base Line. 4/19/00.
    Construction. Left wall exiting campus. June-Sept., 2000.
    Flowers in median buffer. Sept. 2000.
    Sign: Campus Entrance Project Made Possible by Contributions from the UPG Advisory Board and the Student Government Association.
    Fall, 2000.
    [N.B.: curb moved back 10 ft. from the road and island partially removed to allow for easier turns into the campus. Dec. 2008. See: The [UPG] Insider 28 Jan. 2009. No Photo of the Change is in the Archives.]
  - Campus Scenes, 1980-2003 (Map-case 1, Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4, Shelf 11, Box 1)
    [Stationery Note Card. Showing: Millstein Library, McKenna Hall, Lynch Hall, Student Center. Color. Undtd.]
    Spring, 1980
    Summer, 1984
    Spring, Fall, Winter 1985
    Spring, 1986. Heavy snow melt run-off. Prints. Negatives.
    Fall scenes. 1998, 1999.
    Winter 1995. 11/29/95
    Winter scenes. Jan., 1999. Winter, 2002. Dec., 2002.
    Winter snow storm. Feb. 16-17, 2003
    Winter [undtd]
    Mallards. 1999, 2001
    Panoramic View. 5/19/95
    Panoramic view. Chambers Hall, McKenna Hall, Powers Hall, Pedestrian Bridge. Apr., 1999 Fall, 1999.
    Aerial view. ca. 1999-2000. Shows: Millstein Library, Chambers Hall, Smith Hall, Robertshaw Hall, Tennis Courts, Ridilla Field (partial).
    Aerial view of UPG Campus. ca. 2000.
    Campus Scenes [undtd]
    See also: UPG.fRG.60 (filed in Map Case) Includes Aerial View, Apr. 1991 and Architectural renderings of two panoramic views of the campus with one showing parking lot in front of Smith Hall and one not having the parking lot. Framed folio sized photographs. [ca. late 1980's?, early 1990's?]
    See also: Wildlife
    UPG Campus Winter [February 2010] See: UPG.RG.60 FD1
    Flood [Slate Creek Flood 5/16/11] See: UPG.RG.60 CD32.
  - Capitol Steps, April 1, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    Performance at UPG
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG President's Scholarship Fund
  - Carillon [Ferguson Carillon], 1995 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
  - Carter, Coach Ken, March 21, 2005 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    Appearance at UPG
  - Carter, Rubin "Hurricane", February 2000 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    Black History Month
  - Chandalika, 1998 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
  - Chartwells Appreciation Luncheon, June 8, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 4, Box 4)
    [sponsored by UPG Staff Assoc.]
  - Cheer/Dance Team, 2009-2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 5)
  - Cheerleaders, 1969-2008 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 5)
    First team of cheerleaders. 1969/70
    1997/98 1998/99 1999/00 2000/01 2001/02 2002/03 2003/04 2004/05 2005/06 2006/07 2007/08
    2008/2009 [UPG Archives does not hold a print. faz 1/14/10]
  - Children's Literature Conference, 1997-2014 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 5, Box 1, Shelf 11)
    1st., May 2, 1997
    2nd., May 1, 1998
    3rd., May 7, 1999
    5th., May 4, 2001
    6th., May 3, 2002
    7th., May 2, 2003
    8th., May 7, 2004 See also: Oversize Prints.
    9th., May 6, 2005
    10th, May 5, 2006
    11th May 4, 2007 [UPG Archives does not hold any photos for this conference year. faz]
    12th May 2, 2008 See also: Oversize Prints.
    13th May 1, 2009 [UPG Archives does not hold any photos for this conference year. faz]
    14th May 7, 2010
    15th May 6, 2011 See also: Oversize Prints.
    16th May 4, 2012 See also: Oversize Prints.
    17th May 3, 2013 [Env. 1, Prints; Env. 2, Prints; Env. 3, Photo CD; See also: Oversize Prints.]
    18th May 2, 2014 [Env. 1, Prints; Env. 2, Prints, Env. 3, Photo CD; See also: Oversize Prints including Negative Filmstrip.]
  - Circle Dinner [President's Fall Reception for Faculty and Staff], 1997-2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 5, Box 1)
    1997 1998 2001 2003
  - Clinton, Senator Hillary, March 25, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 5, Box 1)
    Presidential Candidate. Democratic Party, Primary Election Campaign Stop, UPG
  - College Day, April 12, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 5, Box 1)
  - Commencement, 1987-2008 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 5, Box 2)
    1987 See: Portraits--UPG Presidents--Chambers, Dr. George Ferguson
    1989, Apr. 23. [First UPG Commencement held at the Sheraton Inn, Greensburg]
    1996 Includes: Prints. Negatives See also: Oversize Prints.
    1997
    1998
    1999 See also: Oversize Prints.
    2000 See also: Oversize Prints.
    2001
    2002 See also: Oversize Prints.
    2003
    2004
    2005
    2006
    2007
    2008
    For video cassettes of Commencement exercises [1990-2006], see: UPG.RG.60 VC V 1990-2006.
    For DVDs of Commencement exercises[2007- ], see UPG.RG.60 DVD7.1- Univ. of Pgh at Greensburg Commencement.
  - Commercial National Bank of Pennsylvania Student Travel Scholarship, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 5, Box 3)
    [2nd $5,000 pledge payment]
  - Conference Place, 2000-2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 5, Box 3)
    [undtd ca. 2000-2003?] CD
  - Construction, 1996-2005 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 5, Box 3, Shelf 11, Box 1)
    Access Road. 1996.
    Drainage Project. June, 2002.
    Road by FOB (Faculty Office Building). Improvements. 1997.
    Road behind Smith Hall. Baseline.
    Road behind Smith Hall. 1998.
    Road Paving Powers Hall, Lynch Hall Areas. May 2005.
    Walkway between Rossetti Int. House and Humanities Academic Village. Sept. 1999.
    Waterline. Brinkerton Rd. 1999.
    Gas lines. 1999.
    Unidentified.
  - Construction/Renovation Projects, 2010-2012 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 5, Box 4, Shelf 6, Box 1)
    Baseball Field [Renovations]
    Baseball Field Bridge/Road Project
    Chambers Hall (video screens installed in Wagner dining hall and Hempfield Room; sidewalk)
    College Hall
    Faculty Office Building (FOB) (L.A. Sears Office)
    Lyceum (new office for student services)
    Learning Resources Center
    Millstein Library (patio, front desk renovations, psychology lab)
    Pedestrian Bridge (high-level bridge renovation)
    Robertshaw Hall (sprinklers installed)
    Rossetti House (code updates)
    Smith Hall (HVAC renovation)
    Softball (construction of a new softball field)
    Sustainable Office and Classroom Building (S.O.C. Bldg.)
    Gatehouse (Baseline for S.O.C. Building)
    Tosatto Bridge/Road Project.
    [See: UPG.RG.35 Ser.: Minutes 3/15/11. Facilities Update Report, 3/3/11. "Status on Current Facilities Projects.]
  - Croquet Tournament, 1999-2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 2, Shelf 11, Box 1)
    Site set up. 1999.
    Tournament. 6/11/00.
    Tournament. 6/6/04. Includes Floppy Disk with 19 photographs.
  - Cross Country (Men's, Women's), 2002-2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 6, Box 2)
    2002/03 Team photo. Individual photos.
    2003/04 Team photo. Individual photos.
    2004/05 Team photo. Individual photos.
    2005/06 Roster 2005
    2006/07 Roster 2006
    2007/08 Roster Fall 2007
    2009/2010
  - Cultura, La, 2002-2007
    - The Life and Times of Leonardo da Vinci, January 19, 2002 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 2)
      Dinner and Reception. Includes pictures of first da Vinci Scholars.
      For video cassette of Dinner and Reception, See: UPG.RG.60 VC III.E; for video cassette of lecture by Dr. Claire Farago, Univ. of Colorado, See: UPG.RG.60 VC VIII.15. See also: UPG.RG.60 DVD24 UPG Campus History.
    - A Paris, 2003 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 2)
      Dinner and Reception. 1/18/03. Lecture series: 1/23/03, Dr. Bradford Collins, Univ. of South Carolina; 1/22/03, Dr. Rosemary Lloyd, Indiana University, Bloomington; 1/30/03, Dr. Edward Muller, University of Pittsburgh.
      See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Cultura, La. 2003 A Paris; for video cassettes of lecture series, see: UPG.RG.60 VC VIII 16A-C; for video cassette of Dinner and Reception, see: UPG.RG.60 VC VIII.F.
    - Noche Espanola. Spain: Origins, Treasures, and Legacy of the Golden Age., January 17, 2004 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 2)
      Dinner and Reception.
      See also: UPG.RG.60 Video Cassettes. VC VIII.17. A-C.
    - Welcome to China, January 13, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 6, Box 2)
      Dinner and reception.
  - Dance Team [UPG Bobcat Dancers], 1998-2008 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 11, Box 1, Shelf 6, Box 3)
    1998/99. Group photo. Individual photos.
    1999/00. Group photo. Individual photos.
    2000/01. Group photo. Individual photos.
    [2001/02] 2001, Nov. 15. Group photo. Individual photos.